cowonamerica.com 2016-05-08

# AutoCapsule

**[ NOTE ]** Many features of this site require Javascript and cookies. You can enable both via your browser's preferences settings.   

Privacy on jetaudio.com - An Overview 

JetAudio, Inc. (JetAudio) is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. Throughout cyberspace, we want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers. The purpose of this jetaudio.com privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to jetaudio.com, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit jetaudio.com, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. 

Other JetAudio products and services may also have their own privacy policies, which you should review when you use these services. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to jetaudio.com, and not to other companies' or organizations' Web sites to which we link. 

Information About All jetaudio.com Visitors 

In general, our site automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to jetaudio.com and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. 

This aggregate data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. For example, jetaudio.com uses a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells us how and when pages in our site are visited, and by how many people. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through these cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your screen name or e-mail address is. We also may provide statistical "ratings" information, never information about you personally, to our jetaudio.com partners about how our members, collectively, use jetaudio.com. We do this so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible Web experience as well. 

Finally, jetaudio.com, its advertisers and ad servers may also use cookies, as well as small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs," to determine on an anonymous basis which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them, but do not use these technologies to collect personally identifiable information unless you give us permission to do so. 

Information About You 

If you are an jetaudio.com member, when you access jetaudio.com you may obtain access to features of the jetaudio.com service that contain personal information. 

Additionally, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service or when you order a product. We will need certain information -- such as name, Internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number -- in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. You can choose not to receive such information if you don't want to by letting us know on the registration screen when you sign up for the product or service. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to respond or not.

Disclosure 

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to jetaudio.com or information that you may give us on jetaudio.com, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. jetaudio.com may share such information in response to legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or in special cases such as a physical threat to you or others. 

And, as we mention above, we may share with our Web site partners aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of jetaudio.com. 

Questions regarding the above statement, visit the 

.

Last updated: October 6, 2010
